What time is it?
[Shindecent]
[Where are you? Sleeping?]
[You're not picking up
Text me when you wake up]
I don't remember
anything
Hey, Soobin
Why am I here?
Hey
How much did you drink
last night?
I don't know
Hyobum forced me
to drink
He brought you here
What?
Hey, did I make a mistake
or something?
You don't remember
anything, do you?
No,
not at all
I'm sorry
Just forget it
We should organize
all of these
Hey, you shouldn't
do it like this
What? You know-it-all?
-You don't need to do this
-Damn, I was almost there
That bastard
messed it up
Didn't you hate smoking?
Why are you here…
It's the last day
of shooting today
so I'm here to cheer
Hyesung
Hey
You don't need to
lie to me
About what?
About your
fake relationship
You don't need to
hide it from me
Why do you think so?
Because I know you
You do whatever
it takes for success